# **Ezequiel Joaquín Zion**

I'm a Fullstack Engineer based in Buenos Aires, Argentina 🚬

I have always strived to understand the *hows* and the *whys* great things are **great**, so that I can implement it in what I produce.

I have a strong passion for design and UX, and intend to make it my field of expertise.

- ▼ >> Let's keep in touch
  - +54 9 11 3323 4385
  - 🔀 Email
  - Marie Github

# **Professional Experience:**

#### **Fullstack Developer**

PSh | Jan. 2021 - Present

- Full time
- Helping produce top-notch functionalities for a US client
- Using React, CSS, TypeScript, Node.js, Redux, PostgreSQL, etc.
- Developing function components from scratch with a keen eye to detail and great UX
- Code reviewing my peers and helping them with debugging and to provide solutions
- Implementing unit and integration tests using Jest
- Working with agile methodologies, with 3-week sprints and daily direct meetings with the client and their team

#### **Website Management**

Country Magazine | May 2020 - December 2020

- Freelance
- · Successfully migrated their website from Joomla to Wordpress
- In charge of designing the look and feel of the site
- Helped restructure how content was presented
- Used HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, FileZilla, cPanel, etc.

## Skills & Knowledge:

- HTML
- CSS
  - Styled Components
- Javascript
  - React
  - Node.js
  - TypeScript
  - Next.js
  - Jest
- Redux
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- Linux
- Figma

### **Education:**

### **Universidad de Buenos Aires**

Computer Science Degree | 2019 - Present

#### **Escuela Técnica ORT**

Programming & Digital Media Specialization | 2013 - 2017

### **Languages**:

- Spanish (native)
- English (<u>C1 CEFR Level</u>)
- Italian (A2 CEFR Level)
- Portuguese

### **Acknowledgements:**

• Was <u>awarded</u> by World ORT in the STEM Communication Awards 2017



You can also check the online version of this resume, which is always up to date

Ezequiel Joaquín Zion 1